His justice comes from the barrel of a gun.
The Outsider is a drama, romance, western film directed by Randa Haines.
Montana sheep farmer Rebecca Yoder offers sanctuary to an on-the-lam
outlaw, Johnny Gault, who is suffering from a gunshot wound.
Yoder is a recent widow, and her decision to help the outsider
doesn't sit well with her Quaker community.
As a romance brews between her and Gault, it puts in
jeopardy her standing among her devout neighbors.
But when an evil rancher makes a play for the community's land, Gault's
sharpshooting skills might prove his worth after all.
Johnny Gault, played by Tim Daly.
Rebecca Yoder, played by Naomi Watts.
Noah Weaver, played by Keith Carradine.
Doctor Lucas Henry, played by David Carradine.
Benjo Yoder, played by Thomas Curtis.
Ben Yoder, played by Brett Tucker.
The Outsider is a 2002 Western television film
starring Tim Daly and Naomi Watts.
The film is based on Penelope Williamson's novel.
It was first aired on Showtime on November 10, 2002.
The tone is emotional.